bookmyflowers.com 2019-03-02

# Privacy Policy

**Note:** This Privacy Policy forms an integral part of the Terms and Conditions other policies, disclaimers etc. available on the Website of BOOK MY FLOWERS and shall be read in conjunction.  
---  
BOOK MY FLOWERS.com **(“Company,” “we”, “us”, “our” or “BOOK MY FLOWERS”)** is the sole owner of the information collected on all BOOK MY FLOWERS Websites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the Website.  
We value the trust you place in us. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices.  
**Note:**  
Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.  
By visiting the Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website.  
By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms and Conditions.  
  
## Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information  
  
When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.  
If you choose to buy on the Website, we collect information about your buying behavior.  
If you transact with us, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit / debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument details and tracking information from cheques or money orders etc.  
If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.  
We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, credit card / debit card / other payment instrument details, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with us. While you can browse some sections of our Website without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests.  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete by emailing our Customer Support at support@BookMy Flowers.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.  
  
## Communications from the Site   
  
#### Special Offers and Updates  
  
We may occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  
  
#### Press Releases and Newsletters  
  
If you request to receive our press release(s) or newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send these documents to you. Out of respect for your privacy, please contact us if you subsequently wish to be removed from this mailing list.  
  
#### Service-related Announcements  
  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email advising you of this.  
Legal Disclaimer  
We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.  
We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms and Conditions or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.  
If you no longer wish to receive our press releases, newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [support@bookmyflowers.com](mailto:support@bookmyflowers.com)  
  
## Cookies  
  
We do not use cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes.  
  
## Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)  
  
We do not use clear gifs (I.e. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) in our HTML-based emails.  
Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users and to let companies know which emails recipients have opened, allowing them to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of their on-line marketing campaigns. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.  
  
## Links to Other Sites  
  
Our Website links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. **BOOK MY FLOWERS** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.  
  
## Advertisements on BOOK MY FLOWERS  
  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  
  
## Security  
  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We do not use any encryption on our forms, as we do not collect credit card numbers, social security numbers or any other sensitive information that can be used in identity theft.  
  
## Business Transitions  
  
In the event **BOOK MY FLOWERS** goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will be among the assets transferred.  
  
## Changes in this Privacy Statement  
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it periodically. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page
